<?xml version="1.0" encoding= "UTF-8"?>

<Home>
	<navbar>
		<title>Gotta Love Cake</title>
		<home>HOME</home>
		<aboutus>ABOUT US</aboutus>
		<menu>MENU and PRICING</menu>
		<masterchefs>MASTER CHEF'S</masterchefs>
		<pages>PAGES</pages>
		<about>About</about>
		<testimonial>Testimonial</testimonial>
		<cake>Gotta Love Cake</cake>
		<contactus>Contact Us</contactus>
		<ourservice>ourservice</ourservice>
		<bento>BENTO CAKE</bento>
		<content4>Solid color design embraces simplicity and focuses on the beauty of a single color. It is a clean and contemporary cake style that relies on a bold and vibrant color choice to create a striking visual impact.</content4>

		<alpha>ALPHABETH LETTER CAKE</alpha>
		<content5>Creative and personalized cake design where the cake is shaped in the form of a letter or letters, typically representing initials, names, or messages.</content5>
		
		<floral>FLORAL CUPCAKES CAKE</floral>
		<content6>It features a clean and sleek cake design with a border resembling brush strokes or paint splatters, reminiscent of a painter's palette.</content6>
		
		<ombre>OMBRE DESIGN CAKE</ombre>
		<content7>Ombre design combines the elegance of simplicity with a gradual transition of colors. It is a sleek and modern cake style that focuses on clean lines and a subtle color gradient.</content7>
		
		<floral>FLORAL BLOOM CAKE</floral>
		<content8>This stunning creation features layers of moist cake, delicately flavored with hints of vanilla or other complementary flavors. Each layer is expertly frosted with a velvety buttercream.</content8>
		
		<suprise>CHOCOLATE SUPRISE CAKE</suprise>
		<content9>At its core lies a moist and rich chocolate cake that serves as the perfect canvas for the surprises hidden within</content9>
		<title>Gotta Love Cake</title>
		<home>Home</home>
		<aboutus>About Us</aboutus>
		<menu>Menu and Pricing</menu>
		<masterchefs>Master Chef's</masterchefs>
		<pages>Pages</pages>
		<contactus>Contact Us</contactus>
		<emailus>gottalovecake@gmail.com</emailus>
		<callus>+639152455984</callus>
		<testimonial>Testimonial</testimonial>
		<delight>Delightfull</delight>
		<gottalovecake>GOTTA LOVE CAKE</gottalovecake>
		<bday>CUSTOMIZE CAKES</bday>
		<funfetti>FUNFETTI CAKE</funfetti>
		<content4>Our Funfetti cake is a celebration in itself, filled with vibrant colors and sprinkles that bring joy to every bite. It's a cake that radiates happiness and brings back childhood memories.</content4>

		<mocha>MOCHA CHIFFON BUTTERCREAM CAKE</mocha>
		<content5>Layered between the moist chiffon cake is our decadent and creamy buttercream frosting infused with a luscious blend of chocolate and coffee.</content5>
		
		<nutella>NUTELLA FERRERO ROCHER CAKE</nutella>
		<content6>At the heart of this masterpiece lies a moist and velvety chocolate cake, generously layered with luscious Nutella cream. The smooth and creamy Nutella filling perfectly complements the decadent chocolate cake, creating a heavenly combination.</content6>
		
		<ube>UBE INDULGENCE CAKE</ube>
		<content7>At the heart of this indulgent creation is a moist and tender ube-flavored cake. Ube lends its unique sweet and nutty flavor, along with its stunning purple hue, creating a cake that is as visually stunning as it is delicious.</content7>
		
		<price6>PHP 200</price6>
		<price7>PHP 1400</price7>
		<price8>PHP 1000</price8>
		<price9>PHP 850</price9>

		<special>Special Combo Pack</special>
		<super>SUPER DELICIOUS CAKES</super>
		<description>Cakes can vary across cultures, contexts, and personal interpretations. The specific symbolism of a cake may also depend on its design, ingredients, and the occasion for which it is created.</description>
		<button7>Shop Now</button7>
		<button10>View More</button10>
		<designation4>Cakes are versatile and can be customized to suit individual preferences and dietary restrictions. They can be made gluten-free, vegan, or with alternative sweeteners. The world of cakes is diverse, with endless flavor combinations, designs, and creative possibilities, making them a delightful treat for any occasion.</designation4>
		
		<getintouch>GET IN TOUCH</getintouch>
		<address>Third Gate,Tanza,Boac, Marinduque</address>
		<gmail>gottalovecake@gmail.com</gmail>
		<telephonenumber>+639152455984</telephonenumber>
		<serv>SERVICE</serv>
		<meet>FIND US</meet>
		<latest>UPDATES</latest>
		<cs>CONTACTS</cs>
		<quicklinks>QUICK LINKS</quicklinks>
		<newsletter>Email Us</newsletter>
		<search>Send</search>
		<description1>All about to search here</description1>
		<button8>Sign Up</button8>
		<site>Gotta Love Cake</site>
		<all>All Rights Reserved</all>

	</navbar>
</Home>


