<?xml version="1.0" encoding= "UTF-8"?>

<Home>
	<navbar>
		<title>Gotta Love Cake</title>
		<home>HOME</home>
		<aboutus>ABOUT US</aboutus>
		<menu>MENU and PRICING</menu>
		<masterchefs>MASTER CHEF'S</masterchefs>
		<pages>PAGES</pages>
		<contactus>CALL US</contactus>
		<emailus>EMAIL US</emailus>
		<email>gottalovecakezone@gmail.com</email>
		<callus>+639152455984</callus>
		<ourservice>Our Service</ourservice>
		<brand>GOTTA LOVE CAKE</brand>
		<testimonial>Testimonial</testimonial>
		<contctus>CONTACT US</contctus>
		<delight>Delightfull</delight>
		<gottalovecake>GOTTA LOVE CAKE</gottalovecake>
		<bestcake>THE BEST CAKE IN MARINDUQUE</bestcake>
		<button1>Read More</button1>
		<button2>Play Video</button2>
		<youtube>Youtube Video</youtube>
		<meet>MEET THE TEAM</meet>
		<greetings>Welcome to Gotta Love Cake</greetings>
		<content>Usually appealing cupcake that incorporates floral elements as decorations. These cupcakes are often adorned with edible flowers, buttercream piped flowers, or fondant flowers to create a charming and natural aesthetic.</content>
		<content1>Using only the finest ingredients, we bake our cakes from scratch, infusing them with mouthwatering flavors that will transport you to dessert heaven. From classic favorites to unique and innovative creations, we offer a diverse range of flavors and styles to suit every occasion and palate.</content1>
		<healthy>100% Healthy</healthy>
		<content2>We offer a range of healthier options, such as gluten-free cakes, vegan cakes, and cakes made with alternative sweeteners. These alternatives are carefully crafted to maintain the same level of taste and texture, while accommodating specific dietary requirements.</content2>
		<award>Award Winning</award>
		<content3>We offer a range of healthier options, such as gluten-free cakes, vegan cakes, and cakes made with alternative sweeteners. These alternatives are carefully crafted to maintain the same level of taste and texture, while accommodating specific dietary requirements.</content3>
		<experience>OUR EXPERIENCE</experience>
		<numbers>12678</numbers>
		<cakespecialist>CAKE SPECIALIST</cakespecialist>
		<numbers1>13456</numbers1>
		<complete>COMPLETE PROJECTS</complete>
		<numbers2>14567</numbers2>
		<clients>HAPPY CLIENTS</clients>
		<numbers3>16789</numbers3>
		<menu1>Menu and Pricing</menu1>
		<explore>EXPLORE OUR CAKES</explore>
		<button3>BIRTHDAY</button3>
		<button4>WEDDING</button4>
		<button5>CUSTOM</button5>

		<funfetti>FUNFETTI CAKE</funfetti>
		<price>P1,300.00</price>
		<content4>Our Funfetti cake is a celebration in itself, filled with vibrant colors and sprinkles that bring joy to every bite. It's a cake that radiates happiness and brings back childhood memories.</content4>

		<mocha>MOCHA CHIFFON BUTTERCREAM CAKE</mocha>
		<price1>P1,099.00</price1>
		<content5>Layered between the moist chiffon cake is our decadent and creamy buttercream frosting infused with a luscious blend of chocolate and coffee.</content5>
		
		<nutella>NUTELLA FERRERO ROCHER CAKE</nutella>
		<price2>P2,358.00</price2>
		<content6>At the heart of this masterpiece lies a moist and velvety chocolate cake, generously layered with luscious Nutella cream. The smooth and creamy Nutella filling perfectly complements the decadent chocolate cake, creating a heavenly combination.</content6>
		
		<ube>UBE INDULGENCE CAKE</ube>
		<price3>P749.00</price3>
		<content7>At the heart of this indulgent creation is a moist and tender ube-flavored cake. Ube lends its unique sweet and nutty flavor, along with its stunning purple hue, creating a cake that is as visually stunning as it is delicious.</content7>
		
		<floral>FLORAL BLOOM CAKE</floral>
		<price4>P1,589.00</price4>
		<content8>This stunning creation features layers of moist cake, delicately flavored with hints of vanilla or other complementary flavors. Each layer is expertly frosted with a velvety buttercream.</content8>
		
		<suprise>CHOCOLATE SUPRISE CAKE</suprise>
		<price5>P1,649.00</price5>
		<content9>At its core lies a moist and rich chocolate cake that serves as the perfect canvas for the surprises hidden within</content9>
		
		<boho>BOHO 3-TIER CAKE</boho>
		<price6>P16,000.00</price6>
		<content10>The Boho 3-Tier Cake is adorned with handcrafted sugar flowers, delicate greenery, and intricate designs inspired by nature. The combination of these elements creates a visually captivating display, evoking the spirit of a bohemian garden.</content10>
		
		<mini>MINIMALIST TWO-TIER WEDDING CAKE</mini>
		<price7>P13,000.00</price7>
		<content11>The elegance of the Minimalist Two-Tier Wedding Cake lies in its simplicity. It can be adorned with delicate touches of fresh flowers, greenery, or a subtle metallic accent, perfectly complementing the minimalist design and adding a touch of sophistication.</content11>
		
		<buttrcrm>BUTTERCREAM WEDDING CAKE</buttrcrm>
		<price8>P14,000.00</price8>
		<content12>Buttercream Wedding Cake is carefully layered with moist and flavorful cake, complemented by a velvety smooth buttercream frosting. Whether you prefer classic flavors like vanilla and chocolate or desire a more adventurous taste, we offer a range of delectable options to suit your preferences.</content12>

		<rustic>RUSTIC SEMI-NAKED WEDDING CAKE</rustic>
		<price9>P17,000.00</price9>
		<content13>Popular style of wedding cake that has a charming and natural appearance. It features a thin layer of buttercream or frosting on the exterior, which is intentionally left uneven or partially scraped off to create a semi-naked effect</content13>

		<tier>CLASSIC THREE-TIER WEDDING CAKE</tier>
		<price10>P19,000.00</price10>
		<content14>If you're dreaming of a towering treat that's not too overpowering, keep the rest of the design simple. Small floral clusters and an elegant cake topper add just enough color to this minimal confection</content14>

		<succulent>SUCCULENT WEDDING CAKE</succulent>
		<price11>P20,000.00</price11>
		<content15>inspired by the beauty of succulent plants. It incorporates elements of these desert plants, known for their unique shapes, colors, and textures. A succulent cake can add a touch of natural elegance and botanical charm to a wedding celebration.</content15>

		<alp>ALPHABET LETTER CAKE</alp>
		<price12>P2,300.00</price12>
		<content16>Creative and personalized cake design where the cake is shaped in the form of a letter or letters, typically representing initials, names, or messages.</content16>

		<miniml>MINIMALIST CUSTOM CAKE OMBRE DESIGN</miniml>
		<price13>P3,000.00</price13>
		<content17>ombre design combines the elegance of simplicity with a gradual transition of colors. It is a sleek and modern cake style that focuses on clean lines and a subtle color gradient</content17>

		<customcake>MINIMALIST CUSTOM CAKE SOLID COLOR DESIGN</customcake>
		<price14>P2,000.00</price14>
		<content18>Solid color design embraces simplicity and focuses on the beauty of a single color. It is a clean and contemporary cake style that relies on a bold and vibrant color choice to create a striking visual impact</content18>

		<pallete>MINIMALIST CUSTOM CAKE PALLETE PAINTING BORDER DESIGN</pallete>
		<price15>P2,500.00</price15>
		<content19>Combines the simplicity of a minimalist style with the artistic flair of palette painting techniques. It features a clean and sleek cake design with a border resembling brush strokes or paint splatters, reminiscent of a painter's palette</content19>

		<floralcake>FLORAL CUPCAKES</floralcake>
		<price16>P700.00</price16>
		<content20> you can try adding floral extracts or essences to the cupcake batter. Popular choices include rosewater, lavender, or orange blossom water. Be cautious not to use too much, as floral flavors can be quite potent. Start with a small amount and adjust to your taste.</content20>

		<bento>Bento Cake</bento>
		<price17>P300.00</price17>
		<content21>preferred flavor, such as vanilla, chocolate, or any other flavor you like. You can use a square or rectangular cake pan to create a shape that resembles a bento box. Allow the cake to cool completely before moving on to the decoration.</content21>

		<bday>BIRTHDAY</bday>
		<wed>WEDDING CAKE</wed>
		<custo>CUSTM</custo>

		<descripbdaycake>The birthday cake is often seen as a gesture of love and appreciation for the person whose birthday is being celebrated. It represents the care and thoughtfulness put into making the occasion memorable.</descripbdaycake>

		<button9>Read More</button9>

		<descripweddingcake>Like a birthday cake, a wedding cake represents joy and sweetness in the couple's life. It symbolizes the happiness, love, and celebration surrounding the wedding day.</descripweddingcake>

		<descripcustomcake>Custom cakes are often created for significant milestones such as birthdays, anniversaries, graduations, or achievements. They symbolize the recognition and commemoration of important events or accomplishments in a person's life.</descripcustomcake>

		<discount>30% DISCOUNT FOR THIS SUMMER</discount>
		<button6>Order Now</button6>

		<team>Team Members</team>

		<chefs>OUR MASTER CHEFS</chefs>

		<namechef1>Riza Mae Ledesma</namechef1>
		<designation>Executive Chef (Chef de Cuisine, Head Chef)</designation>

		<namechef2>Daniel Lorenzo Manahan</namechef2>
		<designation2>Chef-Owner (Group Chef)</designation2>

		<namechef3>Darwin Melaya</namechef3>
		<designation3>Sous Chef (Second Chef, Under Chef)</designation3>

		<special>Special Combo Pack</special>
		<super>SUPER DELICIOUS CAKES</super>
		<description>Cakes can vary across cultures, contexts, and personal interpretations. The specific symbolism of a cake may also depend on its design, ingredients, and the occasion for which it is created.</description>

		<button7>Shop Now</button7>
		<button10>Read More</button10>

		<testiclients>OUR CLIENTS SAY!!!</testiclients>

		<clientname>Renna Mae Regio</clientname>
		<profession>Engineer</profession>
		<comments>"The Funfetti Cake was a burst of flavors! The tanginess of the vanilla paired perfectly with the sweet and slightly tart springkels filling. The cake was moist and had a lovely texture. I would rate it a solid 9/10."</comments>

		<clientname1>Aliza Mariz Rabe</clientname1>
		<profession1>Programmer</profession1>
		<comments1>"The chocolate cake was absolutely divine! It had a rich, intense chocolate flavor that was incredibly satisfying. The cake was moist and the frosting was creamy and not overly sweet. I would give it a perfect 10/10!"</comments1>

		<clientname2>Catherine Dela Cruz</clientname2>
		<profession2>Software Developer</profession2>
		<comments2>"The presentation of the cake was stunning with intricate decorations and layers. However, the taste didn't quite live up to the appearance. The cake was a bit dry, and the flavors were somewhat bland. I would rate it a 10/10."</comments2>

		<clientname3>Cindy Rosales</clientname3>
		<profession3>Computer Engineer</profession3>
		<comments3>"I tried the Succulent Wedding cake, and it was light and fluffy just like I prefer. The vanilla flavor was subtle and not overpowering, which was perfect for my taste. The texture was spot on, and the frosting was smooth and creamy. I would give it an 8/10."</comments3>
		
		<cakezone>Cake Zone</cakezone>
		
		<designation4>Cakes are versatile and can be customized to suit individual preferences and dietary restrictions. They can be made gluten-free, vegan, or with alternative sweeteners. The world of cakes is diverse, with endless flavor combinations, designs, and creative possibilities, making them a delightful treat for any occasion.</designation4>
		
		<getintouch>GET IN TOUCH</getintouch>
		<address>Third Gate,Tanza,Boac, Marinduque</address>
		<gmail>rizamaeledesma@gmail.com</gmail>
		<telephonenumber>+639152455984</telephonenumber>
		<latest>LATEST BLOG</latest>
		<cs>CONTACT US</cs>
		<serv>OUR SERVICES</serv>

		<quicklinks>QUICK LINKS</quicklinks>
		<newsletter>NEWSLETTER</newsletter>
		<latest>Latest Updates</latest>
		<description1>All about to search here</description1>
		<search1>Sign Up</search1>
		<site>Gotta Love Cake</site>
		<all>All Rights Reserved</all>
	</navbar>
</Home>


